Mom...
You're finally quiet.
Sir, just pull over up ahead.
Thank you, Sir.
See you.
Do you think you can get away?
You claimed your mother took the train back,
but there's no record of any ticket purchase.
That means she's still in the city.
Your brother soon realized she was missing.
He probably went to the police.
And the last time...
Just shut up!
Sis, open the door!
Sis!
Open up!
The police need to talk to you!
Sis!
Open the door!
What are you doing in there?
Sis!
Mom is missing!
Hurry and open up!
Sis!
Did you hear me?
Open the door!
Sis!
Do you hear me?
Sis, Mom is missing!
Are you Zhang Xiaomin?
Yes, that's me.
We're from the police department.
We received a report,
and need your assistance with an investigation.
Please come with us.
Zhang Xiaomin, this is the search warrant.
Please verify it.
Zhang Xiaomin,
do you know what we found
in your home?
The quilts and blankets in your closet are gone.
The shower curtain is missing, too.
The floor was mopped spotless.
But...
we found traces of blood
in the bend of your toilet's drainpipe.
That blood belongs to your mother.
According to your story,
after your mother argued with you,
she went back to her hometown.
But these bloodstains...
how do you explain them?
You're working at a law firm
as a paralegal, right?
Since you studied law,
let's not beat around the bush.
You know what dismemberment means.
The site where the body parts were found
was a construction site in the east suburbs.
Two construction workers
on their way home
saw a pack of dogs digging in the dirt.
When they walked over,
they found human remains.
Inside the box containing the remains,
a bloody knife was found.
Testing found your fingerprints on it.
These are photos from the crime scene.
From the body parts dug up from the dirt,
our DNA testing
confirmed that the victim
was a 50-year-old woman,
recovering from breast cancer surgery.
At noon today,
a young man went
to the local police substation to report
that his mother was missing.
She was recovering from cancer surgery.
They spoke on the phone every day,
but today, he suddenly couldn't reach her.
And that young man who reported it
happens to be your younger brother, Zhang Xiaoqiang.
We also questioned your neighbors.
They all said
your relationship with your mother was terrible,
and that you often fought fiercely.
In those arguments, you'd even say things like,
"I'd rather be dead,"
"Leave me alone,"
and "I don't want to be your tool."
And on the night of the crime,
your neighbors said
there was constant noise from your place,
persistent sounds
that went on until around 2:00 a.m.
Footsteps pacing back and forth, too.
How do you explain that?
The rarest thing in this world...
is peace and quiet.
What do you mean?
Parents can choose their children,
but children can never choose their parents.
Nine yuan in total.
Xiaomin.
The verdict from the first trial is coming out soon.
Right now, the best outcome...
might be...
life imprisonment.
I'd rather just get the death penalty.
Zhang Xiaomin!
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
Of course I do.
Xiaomin! Xiaomin!
Is anyone there? The prisoner is suffocating!
Anyone there?
Tomorrow at 11:13 a.m.,
your in-laws will die in a car crash.
Your husband's family is very superstitious.
Ever since their son married you,
he's had nothing but bad luck these past few years.
Behind closed doors, they all say
your failure to conceive
is jinxing the family fortune.
Tomorrow, they'll badger you into going to a temple
to burn incense and pray for a baby.
On the drive back,
your mother-in-law will nag you.
You'll get upset,
pull over to the side of the road and get out.
That's when tragedy will strike.
I'm Fu Ting,
a lawyer.
Though I don't know exactly why,
I've entered your consciousness.
Your consciousness seems quite unique.
Xiaona, I don't mean to criticize,
but look at Xiao Li next door.
She's years younger than Jianguo,
yet she already has two kids.
A boy
and a girl.
Just perfect.
They make a perfect pair.
That's true.
Why don't we look into other options?
Technology is so advanced these days, after all.
It's still better to let nature take its course.
We should just let things happen naturally.
We'll definitely have a child in time.
Mom,
I'm going to use the restroom in the village up ahead.